of 20,000 dollars that help their school programs, whether that be banned or affledding or other
extracurricular events and activities in school district. It's $12,000 a year and the college
gets $8,000 a year. I think we've cut our last check this year or we're really close to it.
And the reason behind those two disbursement checks when we made the change for years ago,
the school district was generating about $12,000 a year in concession money
and because of this change, you know, we went to a private provides per concession,
and the trust authority did not have a school district or those activities to be heard in any way.
Likewise, in the college side, a bail on the athletic apartment was generating about $8,000 a year in
banter sales. And so we've held both of those organizations' partners and for the last four years,
now I think we've cut those checks every fall. We treat our sweet holders like VIP people on
long-range and up and get to eat and have a good time up in the sweet. They all committed a $100,000
student project through those sweet rentals. We've allowed the game to make sure that they have a
really great game-day experience. And so I think maybe not many people really appreciate sort of the
size and the operation of the MTFA. It's a million dollar enterprise at this point in time.
And all of that money, we keep trying to reinvest back into the school and college and the community.
One of really took my hat to Amanda and the CBB. They've been absolutely spot on with bringing in these
major events and major activities. Generate a lot of revenue. And then I've recently talked,
I think a council in the community would be both very surprised and very pleased if you looked at
the amount of hotel beds that get filled because of this facility. I think that information could be
pulled them in. And there's no doubt that that business has doubled or tripled over the last couple
years and she'll tell you a little bit about that and what they're getting ready to do with the ball game. And so
we feel very honored to be able to play a part in trying to help this city be progressive and move forward
and do good things. Literally from kindergarteners up through college aged kids. And so it's important for us
that we have a good working relationship with the council because we really rely on this council to
either reject or approve some of the recommendations that we make. We're always available to come up here
and talk about any of the issues happening that are receiving phone calls if you have questions
and more importantly, if you got ideas on how we can use that facility, we want to hear those as well.
So thank you for that. So box there for two minutes. Well I think it's a important point that this isn't
just the MCFF.
coming to the council for a handout, EMCA, F.A. is doing a lot on its own and for the community.
The scoreboard is a good example of that.
All volunteers on the hands yet.
That's this council.
We're familiar with that.
It's wonderful work when you can get it.
We've got to get it.
You can get it.
Well, the issue with this project is to keep it on that.
I have to get it to set it up.
I felt that had that progress.
Yes, I think that people will start going into it and build it.
Well, it was good to hear all that information.
I mean, it's only information I'd heard is it was a great recruiting tool for the teams.
It's a college team because they had some of those kids from Union or Jinks.
Come down to the work plane here and it's really impressive now.
I will say this to them.
I don't think you had to have a coach and all that hardware up here today had a knock into this.
It had to be recruiting, yeah.
And I've been around college athletics for 30 years and I know a little bit about running college athletic departments.
And there's no way in our conference that we could have this kind of success without having a facility that would both attract and keep those students.
It's a good point.
It works.
And that, again, goes to the Indian experience.
It's the most experienced in that city.
Well, you know, we had the opportunity to me and Neil.
Dean had been there on this both selection committee.
One of the things that I was interested in is, you know, when you talk about both packages and facilities,
what do we up against?
What do we compare with?
Well, I will say after looking at my own personal research that take away the package,
but just facility all together.
It's something to be proud of.
Is it a talking point with a lot of people in town?
Absolutely.
You know, some are angry, some are happy.
But we can always stand around and be stagnant and go nowhere if that's what we choose to do.
So I'm I'm impressed with the facility.
It does add a lot of stuff for us.
I appreciate your guys as volunteer, not just here, but also on the MCFA.
There's, you know, very few handshakes, but a lot of complaints.
Can I have my end of give a little test for a five coach brand and brought them up here?
That has helped a lot of store.
I just hope that you would bring us a fact that the infinite city council is coming in for this game.
Yeah.
We can.
I hope.
So we did a site that's in the finance on Wednesday and in China and some of the more in my office.
And it didn't walk through the stadium and they, you know, took them out on the turf.
And we had press conference earlier that day and they stuck around to go through other duties.
Just took them on the turf.
way, can believe that we had, really had already done the upgrades to the cool plate, but
that really impressed them. Walk them around, take them into the world off, but fall off
or enough, they're going to be able to utilize that to the low game. And I mean, he's the head coach,
walk around and he just kept saying, this is real. Like this is real. Like your high school
has this facility. Walk them through there, show them, you know, the training room that's inside
there. And he was, he's like, we don't have these facilities. And so take them up to the second
week, because we're pretty much putting in a pin that's kind of their administrators and
kind of their dignitaries on the second level on the north side. And they're just walking around
each other like, this isn't it? This isn't normal. This is not what we're used to.
Took them up on the third level. They're ID and President, and it's a long thing he knows how to access
if they're with our corporate sponsors. I mean, they're ID set at one of the round types for me.
She just kept looking around and she said, like, I have no idea you guys have this in my hands. So
she said, I'm using this as a selling point. So we're actually, she's bringing in charter buses.
She's got about 70 folks that have signed up to ride a charter bus for administrators on
Saturday morning, over here next weekend. And then they're offering me to the banquet. And then they're
actually having a social event, the full and theater hall, or an app with their coaches and their
all the kind of stuff she's calling their dignitaries. And it's going to be their council and she can actually
use her class and like, you can work in shifts to take turns of bringing the different council
in and kind of a charter in the game, really prior to the game. And using it as a selling tool for
to see if they're sitting with ever getting on board at this type of a project. So I mean, I
requested two hours on a conference call today and she just, they can't, just with the facilities,
they're blown away, which I think into it, they can't be anything. She's doing quite a bit of their meals.
And when we walk at coach into the cafeteria, you know, I can't do the same work like this,
I mean, I can't do the same work like this. And that's funny because you know, sometimes you
want to throw things out there and try to be in it. But it's called it's a venue on Twitter,
in June to test to the game next weekend is being called the D1 jukeo versus Andy. I mean,
that's what everyone's saying. I'm saying, it's facility wise. I mean, I don't think we realize
it's going to break somebody and I'm going to end it. It just doesn't have anything. We take it for granted.
It's same thing like the pulling theater. We have no idea what it is. We have it here. But this
with facility we have, it's very special. If I can shift in and out to tell them about how you'll
be. The vision of two games that we add here, Quincy, and Texas Parking Base in the
one last month, I talked to both coaches and they said this compares to some of the best
the Japanese state has come up with, he said this is as good for some.
And you know, and I think that's happy, you know, to take that back full circle of why this was brought up tonight is to, and I think it's said it is to continue the momentum.
And that's going to be something for us to consider, especially when you start talking about, you know, do you want to commit to that or do you feel that we need to commit somewhere else?
And I made that comment, well, go, you know, to Vicki and then in many things, but you know, a lot of people always just football football football and it's, um, we're talking about that tonight because we're going to be coming up.
But there is other functions that that facility does for us and you guys talked about that and with this honor plaza having the infield up, you know.
I think you're saying this, to send, to send it to Dana, or just to look at the calendar for the seed.
Just done the 300 days last year.
Yeah, I mean, there is always huge kind of work that we're trying to do.
And on one day, you didn't have five things to go on, and it will be the college, you know, the high school.
Yeah, just talk kind of stuff, come on.
It's really, I do know at that end zone during the high school games, my son is not allowed on there to play cut football, so hey, but I will say during the college games, they can have all the fun, they won't down there on the other end.
I'm appreciate it for that.
Point there, we went that after 15 years, we wouldn't have the eight main game had nothing for this facility.
So, we will be talking about this again on the 19th and if there's any interment of information available, we'll get it out to it.
I'm sure the 19th will be asking you to.
Okay.
I'm 12 as capital ventures, government roll, or any more questions for the law.
I'm from a capital ventures government relations LLC November claim of 3000.
This is Stuart that does basically lobbying work for us.
And we're right in the middle of the license renewal.
We're getting any any updates from him recently.
Not recently.
But I've also asked him to start working with us on the regular line again and trying to get us an inroads with the EPA in relationship with that because
Here's going to start.
To be some very active marketing for the, what's the old steel crack building is right on the side of.
And there is a rail line that goes into that.
So you and I say to represent this in Oklahoma and they're going to start actively marketing that and hopefully creates a job.
So I've asked Stuart to work on that and asked for the others.
Kind of.
really, and I kind of give them stewards some work that we're trying to work on regarding the
re-licensing. That's going to be, I think next week we're going to be starting to talk about
what studies we think are going to be necessary for the re-licensing. What type of prime
framework is going to be looking at and how the RDA and the core bench there's going to be working
together. And then on top of that we're still working quite a bit on getting improvements like
Steve O. Full of R on the 8-year of R. And I know that Benz has been involved in that as well as mine
of Earth's room as well. We keep them a lot this year and I think after the last though,
you realize you need to keep these guys up to speed a little bit more about what he's doing to it.
So we're working hard. Okay. So any questions before we move to a vote?
Okay, do we have much to approve? I'll make a motion to approve. And do we have a second?
No second? Roll call please?
Four strokes? Five? Weston?
Five?
Lewis?
All right.
Johnson?
No.
Short.
Five.
I don't know.
We, uh, went out and said to you, we're for the CME, our portion of the splash land.
We only had two companies that been on and we had HCC and we had back.
We then got a committee together for the four of us.
We judged them off the criteria that they sent us,
what they did.
Like, man, they made 12 splash beds.
HCC.
They don't need to do it too.
They were more into buildings.
And, uh, like, part of the law school is stuff like that.
So after that, we then went to my, uh,
uh, recreation tourism board, CDB.
They recommended for magna.
And we went to the planning commission.
They recommended magna.
We also then, I also then did call three other cities.
And did a background on them.
Um, Colin Field.
I talked to their public board director.
He said they were great to work with.
He would have them do another splash pad with them.
Broke marijuana actually hired them three times.
Did three different splash beds with them.
So, um, we bring it to you guys.
We bring it to you guys.
How do the beds come in?
Uh, as far as on the beds, as with magna and HCC.
Uh-huh.
Um, um, on big portion of it.
All they did when this part of Jesu.
Do we talk about it?
Yeah.
Have we, do we have the beds you had for the war?
No.
So tonight, all you're asking us to do is to approve magnum.
Just like you may.
Any other questions for games?
No.
We have a motion to approve.
I'll make a motion.
And a second?
Second.
Well, call points for Mr.
Hi.
Lewis, hi.
What's did Johnson?
Short.
Hi.
In a new business, no need to business.
Reports are in your pocket.
How about announcements?
Marrying counsel.
I got a bill.
I just want to get some recognition to the man in their staff.
This bill game is wearing a thing.
That's why she signed up for a job.
But they've done a tremendous job.
You all believe what they've done to you.
So I want to thank them.
Well, and I think just to add to that, I don't believe it's going to be done.
But frankly, we wouldn't be talking about this whole thing.
It's going to be like this.
Let's do it.
I don't think we're going to be like that.
So I'm going to.
All right.
Well, I just echo all of that.
I know Dr. Hale does too, because he told me that the other day.
I just want to wish I wouldn't have any thanksgiving.
Okay.
Any other announcements?
City manager.
You can go to the other thing.
I'll just remind everybody that City Office will be closed on Thursday and Friday
and Friday and Friday and Thursday.
So the more staff I know that has to get in.
And a reminder, since this will happen before, and it's a regular counsel meeting as well,
don't forget the Christmas parade on Saturday.
We're going to have that.
And she's both independent and eddo, are both to begin to work.
So that's a good one.
And pancakes.
Yeah.
The water pancakes.
So next weekend.
This.
And that's going to be the answer to the church.
Oh, and that.
The banquet is at what time that December 2nd.
What time is it?
It's at 7.
Go ahead.
I've got a summer.
Any other analysis?
There are none.
Do we have a most strict time?
Yes.
First in church.
Second.